Hey everyone! I received the package from Hong Kong from Dreamask and I'm going to
show you its Sentai today. Sentai is basically a catsuit with gloves and
socks and a hood. So this is going to be first and I absolutely adore this color.
And yes, I'm going to put on the hood later on as well.
So stay tuned for the end of the video.
Before I put it on, I want to point out some things to you.
This is completely made to measure.
So you can customize everything.
I have integrated cups here.
So I'm really curious about them.
And of glove, of glove, of glove, the course.
No, of course the gloves.
As I already said, a zipper in the back.
and it closes the back and the hood.
And by the way, the hood is completely closed from every side.
So this is really going to be interesting.
But let me first put it on.
Enraptured in the sound
Hypernormal frequencies
Illuminating clouds
We televise the noise
To all that we can reach
The broadcast preach the word
Of better times and peace
We automate the lies
I love this color it's so cute and I have to say it feels so silky I mean it's called
silky sentai so you get what you buy so to say what you read but I have the impression that it's
even smoother and silkier than all the other smooth catsuits I tried on so far
and it's really comfortable I mean it's made to measure so it's supposed to fit
like that and I think the fit is really superior funny thing is that the zippers
are like golden also in the back I don't know if you can see it though probably
not because my hair is in the way the cups are not the kind of full cup I'm
used to it's more like a contouring effect but I think it's really cool and
also they recommended it to me when I ordered there I was like ah should I
like take it with the cups or without and they said do the cups they will look
great and they will be good and I think that was the right choice yeah as for
the hood it has a neck panel which is really cool and I'm going to show it to
with hood on I have to like pull it in front of my head behind my head and then
close the zipper but you'll see it in a sec
I want you to stay, I'm begging you please, please don't leave here.
I don't want you to pay for all the hurt that you will feel.
The world is just illusion, trying to change you.
Being like you are, well this is something else.
who would comprehend but some that do they claim divine purpose
okay so what did you think about that tell me in the comments and I'll tell
you a bit more about Dreammask you should definitely check out their store
if you want to satisfy any of your fetishes because they have a lot to
offer they do have latex first of all then of course the Sentai suits but they
also have hoods in any kind and variety and for every scenario you want to play
out for example cross-dressing or yeah animals I think you might have a look
and see what I mean for yourself I think it's really interesting and I mean I
I can't show it to you here because of course it's not really YouTube friendly
so click on the link I put in the description text and check it out yourself.
Alright so thanks for joining me and for watching me trying on this Sentai and yeah
it was a first on my channel here with the hood. I hope you appreciate that
and I hope you're going to check out a lot of my other videos and a big thank you to Dreammask for
for providing me with this suit and for believing in me and your service, telling me some of the tips like the bust curves
and I hope you enjoyed this video as well.
Bye, see you around!
And check out my other videos, a lot more costumes and stuff.